* Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

**PRIVACY POLICY** 

Introduction 

Hinterland Studio Inc. (“we” or “Hinterland”) is committed to being accountable for how we treat personal information and for the principles outlined in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy was developed in compliance with British Columbia’s Personal Information Protection Act (“PIPA”).  PIPA sets out rules for how organizations such as ours can collect, use and disclose your personal information.

We have a designated Privacy Officer that can respond to questions, concerns and complaints at privacy@Hinterlandgames.com  

_Definition of Personal Information_ 

We define personal information as meaning information about an identifiable individual, such as someone’s name, home address, phone number, email, gender, personal preferences about gaming, and personal comments posted on forums. 

_Scope_ 

Our Privacy Policy extends to all of the websites, computer games, forums and on-line stores that we own and operate.

_Purpose_  

We state the purpose of collecting personal information when it is requested. Contact our Privacy Officer for questions about the collection of personal information.  We collect personal information for the following purposes: 

1\. To provide and administer requested products and services, and to disclose the information for any purpose related to operation of accounts and provision of requested products and services;

2\. To communicate with you through our website and email;

3\. To authenticate your identity;

4\. To monitor your compliance with any of your agreements with us;

5\. To provide personal information to third party suppliers of products and services;

6\. To manage or transfer our assets or liabilities, for example in the case of an acquisition or merger, the provision of security for a credit facility or the change of a supplier of products;

7\. To protect us, yourself and others from fraud and error and to safeguard our business interests;

8\. To collect debts owed to us; 

9\. To comply with legal and regulatory requirements; and

10\. To distribute to third parties including financial institutions, payment processors, lawyers, financial institutions and government licensing bodies for any of the above purposes.

_Limits to Collection, Use, Disclosure and Retention of Personal Information_ 

The limits to our Privacy Policy are as follows: 

1\. We will only collect and use personal information that is necessary to fulfill the purposes identified in this policy;

2\. We will not collect, use or disclose personal information except for the identified purposes above unless we received further consent;

3\. We will only collect, use or disclose personal information in accordance with PIPA;

4\. Your personal information will only be used or disclosed for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy and as authorized by law;

5\. We will keep personal information used to make a decision affecting you for at least one year after using it to make the decision;

6\. Subject to the above one-year retention requirement, we will only retain personal information for as long as necessary to fulfill the identified purposes above or as long as required for a legal or business purpose;

7\. We will destroy, erase or make anonymous documents or other records containing personal information as soon as it is reasonable to assume that the original purpose is no longer being served by retention of the information and retention is no longer necessary for a legal or business purpose; and

8\. We will take due care when destroying personal information so as to prevent unauthorized access to the information.

_Consent_ 

We will obtain your consent to collect, use or disclose your personal information, except where we are legally authorized or required by law to do so without consent.   For example, we may collect, use or disclose your personal information without your knowledge or consent where:

1\. The information is publicly available, as defined by statute or regulation;

2\. We are obtaining legal advice; 

3\. We reasonably expect that obtaining consent would compromise an investigation or proceeding; and 

4\. We are permitted to by law.  

Your consent may be provided orally, in writing, electronically or through inaction. Your consent is implied when it is obvious that we are collecting, using or disclosing personal information and when you voluntarily provide personal information for that obvious purpose. Your consent may be implied, express or provided by an authorized individual depending on the nature and sensitivity of the personal information. 

You may withdraw their consent at any time by giving us reasonable notice, subject to legal, contractual and other obligations.  If we receive notice of withdrawal of consent, we will inform you of the likely consequences of withdrawing consent, which may include our inability to provide certain goods or services for which that information is necessary.

_Cookies_

Our websites use cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a website's computer and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Use of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while a user is on our website. We use cookies on certain pages of our site to help analyze our website flow, measure promotional effectiveness and promote trust and safety. We also use cookies to set language preferences. You may set your browser to refuse cookies, but certain parts of our website may not function properly as a result.

_Security of Personal Information_ 

We protect personal information by implementing reasonable security arrangements to prevent against risks such as unauthorized access, collection, use, disclosure, copying, modification or disposal of personal information. We will use reasonably secure methods whenever destroying personal information.  

The protection and security of personal information cannot be guaranteed when it is submitted via email or other wireless communication. 

_Accuracy_ 

We will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the personal information you collect, use or disclose is accurate and complete. Please notify us with corrections if there are any errors or omissions in your personal information.  We will correct the personal information as soon as reasonably possible upon confirmation of the error or omission. We will, as soon as reasonably possible, update your personal information with authorized third parties.

_Access_ 

You have right to access your personal information held by Hinterland Studio Inc. Your request for access must be made in writing and we may require individuals to prove their identity before giving them access to their personal information for security reasons. Upon request and authentication of identity, we will provide information about the ways in which your personal information is or has been used, and the names of the individuals and organizations to which their personal information has been disclosed. 

PIPA allows is to charge a “minimal” fee for providing you with access to your personal information. If a fee is required, we will give you a written fee estimate in advance. 

We will provide requested personal information within 30 business days after it is requested or you will give written notice if you need more time to respond. 

In some cases, we may not give you access to certain personal information where authorized or required by PIPA to refuse access. If we refuse your access request, we will tell you in writing, stating the reasons for your refusal and outlining further steps that are available to you (including any internal review by your organization and the right to ask the Office of the Information and Privacy Commissioner for British Columbia to review the decision). 

_Complaints_

Complaints can be sent to our Privacy Officer at privacy@hinterlandgames.com  

If you are not satisfied with our response to your complaint, you can complain to the Office of the Information and Privacy Commissioner for British Columbia.

### Third Parties

**Google Analytics**

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.

**Spam Defense**

The IPS Spam Defense Service passes the email address and IP address of the registering member to the service to determine the likelihood a registering account is a spam source.

**Invisible reCAPTCHA**

This site uses a CAPTCHA to ensure humans are performing certain actions. The CAPTCHA provider may set a session cookie and get information about your internet browser and device accessing this website.

* Privacy Policy

© 2012-2025 Hinterland Studio Inc.   
"THE LONG DARK", "Hinterland", "WINTERMUTE", the hatchet and the H logo  
are registered trademarks or trademarks of Hinterland Studio Inc.  
All rights reserved.

### COMMUNITY

### BUY THE LONG DARK

### CONNECT WITH US

    * 4.4 Default
        
    * 4.5
        
    * Hinterland 4.7 (updated by DawPi) (Default)

Design with [Veilon.Net](https://veilon.net/)

Copyright © 2012-2024 Hinterland Studio [Powered by Invision Community](https://www.invisioncommunity.com/ "Invision Community")

Important Information
---------------------

We have placed [cookies](https://hinterlandforums.com/cookies/) on your device to help make this website better. You can [adjust your cookie settings](https://hinterlandforums.com/cookies/), otherwise we'll assume you're okay to continue.

  Accept Cookies  Reject Cookies
